Tufts Observer UP055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Observer, 1992 -- 1994; UP055.023; 1 Volumes
  - Tufts Observer, 1992-11-12; UP055.023.023.00010 (Box 23)
    [Admissions, Office of] Unhappy students tend to transfer to Ivy League. pp. 1, 10; Amalgamates nearing its first decade
  - Tufts Observer, 1992-11-19; UP055.023.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1992-12-03; UP055.023.023.00012 (Box 23)
    [Admissions, Office of] Early admissions committee soon to notify class of 1997. pp. 1, 22.Ad Hoc committee on fraternities and sororities. TCU senators question who they represent. pp. 1,2; Vote inconclusive of faculty views. pp. 1, 2.; [Administration] Library, athletics, financial aid, primary focus of new fund drive. p. 1.; Social life needs student action. (edit.) p. 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-01-28; UP055.023.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-02-04; UP055.023.023.00014 (Box 23)
    [Lisa Amatangel] Women's squash looks at top 10, men struggle
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-02-11; UP055.023.023.00015 (Box 23)
    [Alumni relations] Tufts to have jumbofest in April; Activities and Organizations; Little-known group educates campus on sex, p. 2.; [Administration] Budget forum addresses future projects. pp. 1, 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-02-18; UP055.023.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-02-25; UP055.023.023.00017 (Box 23)
    Activities and Organizations; Monty Python Society takes humorous look at Tufts, p.2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-03-04; UP055.023.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-03-11; UP055.023.023.00019 (Box 23)
    Jill Adelman (J 1996). Planning coed Greek House; Jill Adelman (J 1996). Campus needs coed fraternity.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-03-17; UP055.023.023.00020 (Box 23)
    Activities and Organizations; Senate approves FY'94 budget, p.1; Jill Adelman (J 1996). Jumbo phone changes to come.
  - Tufts Observer, [April Fools Day], 1993-04-01; UP055.023.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-04-08; UP055.023.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-04-22; UP055.023.023.00023 (Box 23)
    [Administration 1993] Faculty dodging forum debate. [Administration 1993] DiBaggio and Knable respond to graffiti. [Alaimo, Missy] Former Sports Information Director replaced by Paul Sweeney.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-04-29; UP055.023.023.00024 (Box 23)
    [Administration 1993] Administrative action necessary regarding anti-Semitism, etc. [Administrators Group on Diversity 1993] Students react to Anti-Semitic graffiti. Activities and Organizations; Student groups deserve praise, p.4.; [Administration] Controversial speaker policy overhaul necessary. pp. 5, 6.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-09-02; UP055.023.023.00025 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Amalgamates] A capella groups perform at Orientation
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-09-09; UP055.023.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-09-16; UP055.023.023.00027 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [African-American Orientation] Dial, Tufts perfect match for each other, p. 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-09-23; UP055.023.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-09-30; UP055.023.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-10-07; UP055.023.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-10-14; UP055.023.023.00031 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alcohol Abuse] Freshman drinking at Tufts indication of serious reality.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-10-21; UP055.023.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-10-28; UP055.023.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-11-04; UP055.023.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-11-11; UP055.023.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-11-18; UP055.023.023.00036 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. ['All the King's Men'] 'All the King's' horses trots to Arena Stage.
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-12-02; UP055.023.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1993-12-09; UP055.023.023.00038 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Amalgamates] Bubs, 'Mates', Trunks stage benefit concert
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-01-27; UP055.023.023.00039 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Computer Services 1993-94. Electronic mail to be revamped. [Ad Hoc committee on South African investment] Investment committee prepares for forum. p. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-02-03; UP055.023.023.00040 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-02-10; UP055.023.023.00041 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Activities and Organizations; Cultural concert at Cohen, p.7; [Ad Hoc committee on South African investment] Senate hesitant on reinvestment. P. 3; [African-American Center] Knable begins search for new African American Center director, p. 1.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-02-17; UP055.023.023.00042 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-02-24; UP055.023.023.00043 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-03-10; UP055.023.023.00044 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-04-01; UP055.023.023.00045 (Box 23)
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-04-14; UP055.023.023.00046 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American association of University professors] Custodians get vote of confidence
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-04-21; UP055.023.023.00047 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni relations] Jumbofest to take place on quad
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-04-28; UP055.023.023.00048 (Box 23)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Wendy Abraham. Elected chair of special projects committee (Tufts Community Union); [Adler, Emily] Elected education committee chair (TCU). P.3.
- Tufts Observer, 1994 -- 1996; UP055.024; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of loose copies of the Tufts Observer newspapers, dated from September 1, 1994 to November 21, 1996. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. The Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-09-01; UP055.024.024.00001 (Box 24)
    Wessell [library] gets $21 million facelift. New Hillel Center Close. New UNICCO [University Cleaning Company] workers ease into University setting. DiBiaggio stresses Community service to 1170 freshmen. Engineering school professor [Earle Littleton] dead. Jumbos Sports Makes Giant Strides. Pachyderms [men's and women's cross country] set to Trample Competition. Jumbos to 'air it out' at flag football tourney. [Men's] Soccer catching the fever. Women's tennis team going crazy about retuning eight.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-09-08; UP055.024.024.00002 (Box 24)
    [Alumni lounge] Alumni give kids smiles for Christmas; President Bush to pay Tufts October visit. Vet School Mass. Sign Deal. Senate preps for first Fall meeting. TUPD [Tufts University Police Department] takes hard line on crime. Fall festival brings sober fun to campus Sunday. Teacher Warrior [Elizabeth Ammons] Faces Dean's Battle. Conference Bureau Spends Busy Summer. [Volleyball] Bump, Set, Spike. Field hockey stopper sees skill in '94 squad. Jumbos [women's soccer] set high goals.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-09-15; UP055.024.024.00003 (Box 24)
    [Amalgamates] Long lines worth wait for concert; Tufts safety shuttle runs revised routes, schedules. Engineers celebrate centennial. Fall fest starts new tradition. TCU [Tufts Community Union] Senate VP [Scott Rosenblum] resigns at first meeting. Dukakis to address political scientists. EPIIC [Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship] has perfect vision for 10th anniversary. Referendum planned for Reps' voting rights. Hillel Administrator [Lisa Reichstein] Ready For Move. Fares Foundation Brings Bush To Campus. Sports Focus: Paul Sweeney. Volleyball team California dreamin'. Jumbo soccer has a ball with opponents. Jumbos tennis dodged by terriers. Tufts sailing team looking to breeze past choppy waters.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-09-22; UP055.024.024.00004 (Box 24)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] [Alpha Omicron Pi] Let the games begin; Nutrition Center Renamed. Fee Seeking Recognition for Financial Aid Group. University Avoids Deficit Spending, Nets $1.4 million. Balloting for Senate to take Place Today. New Social Policy Effective in Early Going. Tufts Students Earn Record Number of Fullbrights. [Activities and Organizations] Let the [Greek] Games Begin. p.2; Former Observer Editors Recall Good Times. The NFL Dazzles in its Debut at Tufts (football). Jumbos [volleyball] Bumped by California Opponents. Lyons, Camels and Elephants, Oh my! (women's soccer). Womens cross country tallies fourth at Bryant. [cross country) Men Run Wild. Tufts [men's] soccer smokes camels. (tennis) Women Smashed by Williams, 7-2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-09-29; UP055.024.024.00005 (Box 24)
    [Alumnae Lounge] Singers caputre essence of all kinds of music; Curtis Hall Coffee Shop Proposal Gains Support. KSA [Korean Students' Association] students caught embezzling. Committee agendas set at Senate retreat. Shuttle rescheduling met with criticism. APSA [American Political Science Association] honors Tufts faculty for publication. Tisch ceremony highlights parents' weekend. Treasury Cashes in With [David] Backman. Singers Capture Essence of All Kinds of Music. Tufts Football: Brown and Blue banking on bashing bates bobcats. Tufts Flies Past Continentals, 35-32. Big [football] Play Go Jumbos' Way. [Football] Emerging the the 'Nick' of Time. [Greg] Peters Not Just a Passing Fad. Jumbos [football] Look South, Come Up With [Coach Samko] Late Game Losses Led to Frustrating '93 [football] Season. [Women's] Pachyderms [soccer] pounds Mules Into Mud. Women's soccer Issues Brandeis Disappointing Verdict. Pachyderms [field hockey] Short Circuit [MIT] Engineers. Sailors Lower Boom on Opponents. Pachyderms [volleyball] not very 'Eph'ficient. Tufts cross country run down by opposition. Tufts tennis team tramples trio (women's tennis). Men's Soccer Outlasts Stubborn Mules in Overtime. Jumbos Soar Over Eagles (men's soccer).
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-10-06; UP055.024.024.00006 (Box 24)
    Fireworks Display Coming to Tufts. Motive Unknown for Hillel Bombing. School Breaks Ground for Library. Members of Faculty Object to Bush Lecture. Senate Approves of New KSA [Korean Students Association] Budget. Everything's Pearly for [Pearl] Robinson. Biology Department gets $1.8 million. Ex College Plans Innovative Programs For 30th Anniversary. Jumbos [Men's Cross Country] Overruled by Judges. [Cross Country] Women Run Wild Over Falcons. Loss Ends [field] Hockeys' Three Game Streak. [Women's] Tennis Tumbles, Drops Three Straight. Tufts Volleyball Gets Slammed. [Nick] Alford Shines as Jumbos Blast Bates (football). Tufts [Men's] Soccer Splits Parents Weekend Matchups With Bobcats. Jumbo Fans in 'The Zone'. Tufts [Men's Soccer] Blanks Beavers 1-0. [Allocations Board] Senate approves new KSA budget, p. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-10-13; UP055.024.024.00007 (Box 24)
    [Former Gov. Michael] Dukakis lectures in Poli-Sci classes. Senators create evaluation guide. Rep. Markey coming to Tufts next. Tufts obtains permit to launch fireworks. TLGBC [Tufts Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Community] honores national coming out day with rally at Ballou. [Michaela] Murphy Gets Ready to Show Off 'Baby'. Phi Sig Sig [Sorority] Gains House, Rejoins Greek Scene. Tilton Fire Highlights Fire Prevention Week. Field hockey rudely awakened by Bowdoin. Brown and Blue blast crimson, bow to Bowdoin (Women's tennis). Jumbos' loss un'bear'able (Women's soccer). Brown and Blue [Football] Bitten by Bowdoin Polar Bears. Sports Focus: Mark Mendelblatt. Cross Country Falls Prey to Riverhawks. Gambsy great as men notch eight (Men's soccer). Volleyball dominates in Bowdoin invite. Men's X-country victorious at Babson invite;ranked 25th nationally; [Adler, Emily-head of TCU senate Ed committee] Senators create evaluation guide. p. 1, 6.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-10-20; UP055.024.024.00008 (Box 24)
    JumboTel Change Proposed. World Civ. Requirement Comes Under Fire. A 'Picture' Perfect Weekend. High Demand Limits Seats for Undergrads. Senate passes parking shortage resolution. Religion department future uncertain. King Rules at Tufts public safety. Seniors' Vienna table serves good Cheer. Markey Makes Tufts campaign Stop. Talking about Sex [AIDS awareness week]. Jackson Alumna Praises Handling of Hydro-Quebec. [Professor] Der Manuelian brings Armenian Art into mainstream. President Bush Extends plans for next week's visit. Jumbos Tri-Tri-Tri again [women's soccer]. Golfers Looking Fore 'Par'fection. Jumbos football still Bantam Weights. [Field] Hockey Dams net to Defeat Beavers. UCONN too Husky for pachyderms [women's tennis]. Crew conquers Connecticut, to Chase Champs at Charles. Sports Focus: Mike Gamsby. Jumbos Calculate [men's soccer] Win over Engineers. Jumbo Volleyball on Fire. Men [cross country] stumble to 17th at NEIAA. Harriers to run race for ACS. Football seeks near flawless effort. Women's soccer hoping to reverse Fortunes in Homecoming showdown. Field Hockey seeking upsets over Ephs. Men's soccer ready for Williams showdown. [Nancy] Kerrigan, [John] Hannah To Receive Achievement Award at Tufts.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-10-27; UP055.024.024.00009 (Box 24)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Halloween on the Hill full of fun; Bush Touts Middle East Victory. Many sides Heard At Cuban Forum. Hunter, Religion remain in Limbo. Engineers Unveil New F.C. Nelson Auditorium. Child Study Prof Practices what He Teaches. Halloween on the Hill Full of Fun. Ex College Loses popular professor. Residents recover from Haskell Blaze. Senator Explains Parking Changes. Safety Shuttle Driver reveals all. Choosing the Sack over the Stairmaster. OverKilling our Freedom of Speech. 'Baby' Showcases Tufts musical theater talent. Woosh! In one Flush, Toilet Bowl Swallows Student. [Nancy] Kerrigan, [John] Hannah Presented Awards. Golf Team King of Hill, Beats Williams. Tournament Too Tough A Test For Tufts Tennis Team. Jumbo Cycling Shifting Gears. Tufts [football] fails to Pass against Ephmen. Purple Cows' Milk Jumbos spirit. Jumbos field hockey tames by Lyons; Tipped By Purple Cows. Women's Cross Country Places Sixteenth with sweet finish. Volleyball's streak reaches Lucky 13. Men's soccer gets an 'A' for 'Eph'fort. Crew stuck in Middle at head.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-11-03; UP055.024.024.00010 (Box 24)
    Conference Tackles Media Stereotyping. DiBiaggio Hosts International Reception. A Peaceful Performance. All University Council Students selected. Fletcher Dean Search Produces Five Candidates. UNICCO [University Cleaning Company] Lays Off Custodians. Late-Night Study opens. Malka Manufacture Magnificence with Music. Call it Tufts' Own Campaigning. Future of World Civilizations Debated by Faculty. Jumbos sports need fiercer fight song. Weather Can't Freeze Social Life. The Winter's Tale Chilling show of Emotions. Tuftonians keep rolling along. B&G Encounter Leads to touching experience. [volleyball] Women Play Waiting Game. X-Country Breaks Down at NESCACs. Lord Jeffs [football] Run Wild Over Jumbos. [cross country] Women Stumble in Disappointing Finish. Amherst [women's soccer] Hammers Tufts. [field] Hockey Blanks Amherst, Earns ECAC [Eastern College Athletic Conference] Bid. [Katie] McDowell not to be out dunn. [men's] Soccer psyched for second shot. All-University Council students selected.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-11-10; UP055.024.024.00011 (Box 24)
    Tufts [men's soccer] Looks to Leave Blue Jays Blue. Culture Rep Debate Elicits Student Anger. Tufts Maintains Academic Standards for Recruitment. Concert Band Announces Fall Show. Trustees Approve Downtown Biomedical Research Complex. Tufts embarks on $400M fundraiser. Education Committee Commences World-Civ Re-evaluation process. Call Her The Dean Of Miracles. Tufts ROTC [Reserve Officers' Training Corps] Honors Past Veterans. Jumbo II Missing Tail. Major Changes Yield New Major. You Don't Need to Drink To have Fun. Insanity should be no excuse for Crime. Registration Sparks Fear of Future Plans. Supershow Debut Great Start for Tufts' A Cappella Group. Salim Krimsky Makes Tufts' Music Fun. Tisch Gallery displays Latest Work 'Cafe A'. Albino Squirrel Not as Innocent As Its White Fur Suggests. Football Drops Fifth Straight. Offense Hibernates against Polar Bears [field hockey]. Wildman leads [cross country] Women to Sixth Place at ECACs. The sound and the 'Feury' [men's soccer].
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-11-17; UP055.024.024.00012 (Box 24)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] LCS [Leonard Carmicheal Society] and AEPi team up fo rfaculty Waits-On-You dinner; Nobel Winner [Elie Weisel] Cancels Tufts Date. Tufts Sports Have a Bright Future. Evaluation Guide due out tomorrow. Conference Draws 74 Professors. Logan Airport Turkey Shuttle Returns for Thanksgiving Travelers. LCS [Leonard Carmichael Society], AEPi [Alpha Epsilon Phi] Team up for Faculty-Waits-on-You Dinner. Johnson Just Beginning a New Journey. The Tale of Jumbo II's Missing Tale Comes To an End. Democrats Left, Republicans Right. Tales of Teeth, Tongue, and Tape. Sports Worthy of Praise. Latest 3P's Production Roaring Reality Reflection. Austin Texas Rides Strong At Tufts. Campus Center Food Spreads Rear End Rash. [Football] Panthers Pounce on Pachyderms, 39-19. Northrop [men's cross country] Paces Jumbos in NEs. Sailors Sink To Second. Heartbreaking [men's soccer] Loss Ends Dream Season. Jumbos [men's] soccer Takes Fans on Ride of Their Life. Women's cross country Ends Year in Stride.
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-12-01; UP055.024.024.00013 (Box 24)
    [Alumni] Faculty make suggestions for future of Tufts religion; Deans Without Answers at Forum. DiBiaggio Criticized by Faculty. Hillel Center Opens Today. Endowment Still Suffers From Historical Neglect. Tufts' Community Relations Strained. Course Evaluation Guide Found to Be Mere Puzzling Than Helpful. [Nathan] Gantcher a Devoted Trustee to Tufts. Faculty Make Suggestions For Future of Tufts Religion. Students Feast on More Than Turkey for Break. Pachyderms Lose Wind In Their Sails. Ice Hockey Melts Against Competition. Men set to Make Waves THis Season [swimming]. Northrop Went South T0 Race in [cross country] Nationals. Eight [teams] is Enough [For Men's Basketball]. With New Coach [Janice Savitz] and Enthusiasm, Women Hoop for Best. [Men's Basketball] Watching Out for Charging Moose. [Dan] Ragsdale to Riches. [Jodi] Beach not ready To Throw In Towel [Women's Basketball].
  - Tufts Observer, 1994-12-08; UP055.024.024.00014 (Box 24)
    Grannoff-Hillel Center Unveiled. Alumni Give Kids Smiles For Christmas. Police Take Steps Against Vandals. Evaluation System Set for Administrators. Pancake Breakfast Slated For Tuesday. Dental School Starts Searching For New Dean. Hillel's Future Bright With [President Jason] Weingram. Tufts Sports Adding Jumbos Spirit on Hill. Tufts Lacks Ideological Discussion. Semester Plans Produce Anxiety. Cakes are Cookin' for the O[bserver] in '95. DiBiaggio's Dog reported Missing After Sigma Nu Bash. 'Pool'ar Opposites [Swimmers Mixed Results]. Women [in Track] Quick Out of Blocks. Men's Indoor Track Third Season Opener. Jumbo [Ice] Hockey Fit to Be Tied. Jumbos [women's Basketball] Streak 6-1. Rebounding, Depth Pace Women's [basketball] Wins. Men Re'Maine' Undefeated [In Basketball].
  - Tufts Observer, 1995-01-26; UP055.024.024.00015 (Box 24)
    Tilton [Hall] Becomes All-Frosh. Administrators Share Vision With Freshmen. Students Escape Kobe Quake's Devastation. Senate passes New Constitution. Eliot-Pearson Not Kidding Around With Renovations. [General John R.] Galver Named Fletcher Dean. [Professor Pierre] Laurent Reflects on Teaching, Future. Greek System Girding For Rush Week. Tufts Loses Great Friend, Supporter in [Harrold O.] Zimman. [Harrold] Zimman Youngest Broker, Student Notary in All State. Tufts Still Searching For New Housing Director. Tufts students Prepare Dramatic Spring Season. Brubeck Tickle Ivories at Tufts. Squash Squad Racqueting Up Wins. Women [basketball] Walloped by Wesleyan, Wellesley. Swimmers Warm Up in Caribbean. [Ice] Hockey Heat Up Over Winter Break. Pachyderms Sprint to First and Second Place [Track] Finishes. Mixed Blessing: Men Kneel before Trinity, Beat Albertus Magnus [Basketball].
  - Tufts Observer, 1995-02-09; UP055.024.024.00016 (Box 24)
    [David] Brinker Makes Plea for Greater Student Influence on Campus. Student Life Focus of Trustees' Meeting. Fans to Stage Rally For Hoopsters Tomorrow Night. Colleagues bid adieu to [Nelson] Gifford. Reitman Calls Fraternity Rush Poster Free speech. [Bill] Meserve: Like Father, Like Son. Coedification met with many Protests. Tufts: Hill Freezes Over. All's Well that Enz[o campus barber] Well. Museum Students Overwhelm with 'The Unexpected'. Student Bombarded By Beans Near Ballou. Track Treks to Terrier Town. Jumbos [basketball] Cripple over Continentals, Show Might Over MIT. [men's basketball] Tufts vs. Williams: Clash of the Titans. R-E-S-P-E-C-T: Hockey Team Beats New Hampshire College and Wesleyan; Extends Current Streak to Nine. Jumbos [women's basketball] Smoke Mt. Holyoke. Jumbos [squash] squashed in Storm.
  - Tufts Observer, 1995-02-16; UP055.024.024.00017 (Box 24)
    Trustees Move Toward 'Student Centered' University. Trustees Approve 4.4% Tuition increase. TCU [Tufts Community Union] Senate Tables Mitsubishi Debate. New Intramural Gym in the Works. [Armand Mickune-Santos is] Helping People Help Themselves. Pan-African Alliance Keeping Busy. Fletcher School Continues its growth. Medical School Loses Professor. TUPD [Tufts University Police Department] combats Car Thefts. Orchestra Performances Delight Listeners. Storyteller tells Tales of Black History. Decor of New Student Center Appeals To Many. Squash Teams Exceed Season's Expectations. Hockey Will Stay On Hill. Track On Pace for New Englands. Jumbos [hockey] caught dozin', don't Get Dozen. Women [basketball] Tripped by Trinity, Smash Smith. Hoops Hysteria Hits Hill. Men [Basketball] Beat Bates, 101-98; Women[ basketball] Win, 79-76. [Eric] Emmerit Reaches 1,000 [points]; [Chad] Onofrio, [Chris] McMahon Grab National Honors. [Alcohol and Health Education] Helping People help themselves.
  - Tufts Observer, 1995-02-23; UP055.024.024.00018 (Box 24)
    Tufts Mulls Boston Medical Merger.; [Admissions, Office of] Admissions Process On Schedule. p. 1.; [Joycelyn] Elders Accepts Invitation for Tufts Appearance. It Isn't Easy Being Green, But Tufts is Taking the Lead in Environmental Policy. [Eric] Chapman's a True Role Model. Student Outreach Gears For Open House. Tufts' Presidents Have Shown the Way. Students Plugged Into University System With Dorm Wiring. Student Empowerment Subject of Next All-University Council Meeting. What To Do in a S-not So Good Experience. Track [Team] Impressive at New Englands. Men [swimming] Prepare for Nationals. Clubb Volleyball Set With New Coach. Hockey Fit to Be Tied. Seniors Shine in [women's basketball] Home Finale. Women's swimming Makes a Splash at NEs, Places 5th. Jumbos [men's] Hoops: a Family affair. Disorder in the [basketball] Court. [All-University Council] Student empowerment subject of next meeting.
  - Tufts Observer, 1995-03-02; UP055.024.024.00019 (Box 24)